Inventory of the Papers of Duke and Duke 1854-1956
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Case Files
  - 1930's
    - C. S. Kie Estate 1937 (Box 96)
    - Killian v. Steger 1931-1932 (Box 96)
    - Kimble v. Culbertson 1937-1938 (Box 96)
    - King v. Model Steam Laundry 1934 (Box 96)
    - Kolbe v. Asborn 1933 (Box 96)
    - Kolbe v. Charlottesville Restaurant 1933 (Box 96)
    - Kolbe v. Chesapeake Restaurant 1933 (Box 96)
    - Kolbe v. Monticello Coffee Shop 1933 (Box 96)
    - Lacy v. Gimbert 1935 (Box 97)
    - Lamb v. Huffman 1931 (Box 97)
    - Lane v. Moffitt; Peerless Mattress Co. v. Lane 1937 (Box 97)
    - Leake v. Beagle 1937 (Box 97)
    - Leake v. Carter 1935 (Box 97)
    - Leake v. Perry 1938-1943, 9 folders (Box 97)
    - LeGear Medicine Co. v. Hudson 1932 (Box 97)
    - Letters re interest due, Jan. 1, 1931 1930 (Box 97)
    - Marks v. Groniger 1936 (Box 97)
    - Marshall v. Belk 1933-1935, 2 folders (Box 97)
    - McCann v. Witherow 1937 (Box 98)
    - M. D. and E. M. McClammer 1939-1946 (Box 98)
    - Hunter McGuire McCreery 1931 (Box 98)
    - McDonald v. M. E. Gillioz, Inc. 1937 (Box 98)
    - James McGraw, Inc. v. Walker Iron Works 1931 (Box 98)
    - Midland Finance Corp. v. H. M. Herson Department Store 1933 (Box 98)
    - Miller v. Byard 1933 (Box 98)
    - Monticello Dairy 1931-1936 (Box 98)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Gentry 1938-1940 (Box 98)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Simpson 1938 (Box 98)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Walton 1937-1938 (Box 98)
    - Bessie Lee Morris Estate 1936 (Box 98)
    - Morris Brothers 1930-1931 (Box 98)
    - Mullins v. Moore 1937 (Box 98)
    - Mundy v. Bethard 1932 (Box 98)
    - National Bank of Washington v. Snead 1931 (Box 98)
    - A. S. Nowlin and Co. v. Charlottesville Lumber Co. 1931 (Box 98)
    - Pacific Coast Borax Co. v. Fuller Drug Co. 1933 (Box 98)
    - Pacific Indemnity Co. re Thomas McNeil 1932 (Box 98)
    - Perry v. Gofney 1936, 1946 (Box 98)
    - Perry Coal Co. v. Underwood 1931 (Box 98)
    - Public Indemnity Co. re McDaniels v. Charlie 1932-1933 (Box 98)
    - Quarles v. Dent 1938 (Box 98)
    - Raynes v. M. E. Gillioz, Inc. 1937-1940, 2 folders (Box 98)
    - W. H. Raynor 1938 (Box 99)
    - Reardon v. Government Employers' Insurance Co. 1939-1940 (Box 99)
    - Reiter v. Shoemaker 1939 (Box 99)
    - Rex Manufacturing Co. v. Community Drug Store 1933 (Box 99)
    - Rives Estate 1935-1937, 18 folders (Box 99-100)
    - Romm v. Gray 1936 (Box 100)
    - John A. Ruffalo re James Watson 1930 (Box 100)
    - St. Christopher's School v. Dinwiddie 1938 (Box 100)
    - Schernickow v. Wood 1931-1932 (Box 100)
    - Schreiner v. Mott 1931 (Box 100)
    - Schwartz and Son v. Chellis 1935-1937 (Box 100)
    - Sedge Hill 1935-1942 (Box 101)
    - Shelby Mutual Plate Glass and Casualty Co. 1932 (Box 101)
    - Cornelius Shiflett 1937 (Box 101)
    - Shiflett v. M. E. Gillioz, Inc. 1937 (Box 101)
    - Shinn v. Haines 1938 (Box 101)
    - Skinner v. Calhoun-Watts Motor Co. 1931 (Box 101)
    - Smith v. Tillema 1930's (Box 101)
    - Smith v. S. & R. Silk Mills, Inc. 1931 (Box 101)
    - Snead v. Frank Ix and Son, Inc. 1937 (Box 101)
    - Source Research Council, Inc. v. Smith 1933 (Box 101)
    - Sam Spradlin--Lafferty Farm 1937-1941 (Box 101)
    - R. N. and L. A. Stephens 1930-1950 (Box 101)
    - Stepp v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1935-1937 (Box 101)
    - William M. Thomas 1932-1933 (Box 102)
    - Thomas v. Thomas c. 1932 (Box 102)
    - Christian Thompson 1938 (Box 102)
    - Tucker v. Frisco Railway 1939 (Box 102)
    - Universal Book and Bible House v. Hardy 1936-1939 (Box 102)
    - University Motors 1933-1936, 4 folders (Box 102)
    - University of Virginia v. Johnston-Willis Hospital 1938 (Box 102)
    - Vassar v. Graham 1935-1936 (Box 102)
    - Virginia School Supply Co. v. University Baptist Church 1936-1938 (Box 102)
    - Hattie Walker 1933 (Box 102)
    - Walker v. Bethel 1932 (Box 102)
    - Washington v. Brown 1932 (Box 102)
    - Douglas Watt 1937-1939, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Watt v. Bates 1938 (Box 102)
    - Weaver v. Coiner 1931 (Box 102)
    - Weaver v. Nester 1936-1937, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Harvey E. White 1938 (Box 103)
    - Mary C. White 1930 (Box 103)
    - White v. Bergstresser 1937-1938 (Box 103)
    - Whiting Oil Co. v. Herring 1938-1941 (Box 103)
    - Wiley v. Carson 1934 (Box 103)
    - Williams v. Shope 1937-1938, 11 folders (Box 103-104)
    - Willis v. Walton 1937 (Box 105)
    - Wood v. Wall 1938 (Box 105)
    - Carson Wright 1936-1943 (Box 105)
    - Wyant v. M. E. Gillioz, Inc. 1937 (Box 105)
    - York v. Piedmont Oil Co. 1934-1935, 3 folders (Box 105)
    - Roy Yowell 1931-1939 (Box 105)
  - 1940's
    - Allen v. East 1947 (Box 106)
    - Janet C. Ambler Estate 1940-1945 (Box 106)
    - Amick v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 106)
    - Nannie Anderson Estate 1948-1950 (Box 106)
    - Arnette v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 106)
    - Austin v. DuPont 1947 (Box 106)
    - Baker v. Smith 1948 (Box 106)
    - Banks v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948-1949 (Box 106)
    - Barksdale v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1949 (Box 106)
    - Barnette v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 106)
    - Beasley v. Fisher 1948-1949 (Box 106)
    - Beatty v. Connors Estate 1942-1948 (Box 106)
    - Gilmer R. Belle 1945 (Box 106)
    - Bilyeu v. Simmons 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Bolling v. Mahon 1947 (Box 106)
    - Bolling v. Bolling 1949 (Box 106)
    - Brady v. Deane 1946-1947 (Box 106)
    - Breazeale v. Wyant 1948 (Box 106)
    - Brechin v. DeJarnette 1942-1943, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Bridgeford v. Ott 1949 (Box 106)
    - E. A. Brooks Estate 1948 (Box 106)
    - Mary Elizabeth Brooks 1947-1950 (Box 106)
    - John A. Brown 1946-1948 (Box 106)
    - Buck v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948-1949 (Box 107)
    - Burgess v. Central Electric and Gas Co. 1948 (Box 107)
    - Burkett v. Royal Insulation and Construction Co. 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - C. & F. Theatres Inc., v. Duke 1947 (Box 107)
    - Carter v. Carter 1949 (Box 107)
    - Carter v. Laird and Co. 1947-1948 (Box 107)
    - Carter v. Volm 1949 (Box 107)
    - Carver v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 107)
    - Carvey v. Palmore 1948 (Box 107)
    - Cary v. Augustine Insurance Co. 1948-1949 (Box 107)
    - Central Electric and Gas Co. 1948 (Box 107)
    - Russell S. and Alice Chapman 19443-1953 (Box 107)
    - Sgt. D. R. Ciccotelli 1949 (Box 107)
    - Clay v. Sadler 1947 (Box 107)
    - Cleary v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948-1949 (Box 107)
    - Clemons v. Clemons 1946 (Box 107)
    - Isaiah and Jane Coles 1943-1944 (Box 107)
    - Collier v. Dapkunas 1947 (Box 107)
    - Walter Collier 1948 (Box 107)
    - Collier v. Birkenhead 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Dowell 1949 (Box 107)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Johnson 1949 (Box 107)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Maury 1949 (Box 108)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Ragland 1949 (Box 108)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Reynolds; Unruh v. Reynolds 1942 (Box 108)
    - Conn v. Herndon 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Clyde Corder--New Culpepper Mills, Inc. 1948 (Box 108)
    - Crawford v. Crawford 1948 (Box 108)
    - Crawford v. Pure Oil Co. 1947 (Box 108)
    - Crenshaw v. Crenshaw 1941-1945 (Box 108)
    - Critzer v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948-1949 (Box 108)
    - Cubbage v. Moseley Brothers 1940 (Box 108)
    - Cubbage v. Saunders Electric Co. 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Cugini v. Mills 1940-1941 (Box 108)
    - Davis v. Bradley 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Dew v. Stanton 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Robert P. Dickinson 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Celia P. Downing 1948 (Box 108)
    - Downing v. McNett 1947-1948 (Box 108)
    - Duke v. Pioneer Tailors 1947 (Box 108)
    - Duke v. Railway Express Agency 1947 (Box 108)
    - Duke v. Turner 1941 (Box 109)
    - Duke v. Uttinger 1949 (Box 109)
    - Dorothy Dulin 1943-1945, 3 folders (Box 109)
    - Durham v. Pace 1947 (Box 109)
    - Evey v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1941-1942 (Box 109)
    - Ezekial and Weilman Co. v. Smith 1941-1942 (Box 109)
    - Farish v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948-1949 (Box 109)
    - Fertig v. Wells 1948 (Box 109)
    - Fischer v. Scottsboro Bus Line 1948 (Box 109)
    - Fleming v. Brown 1947 (Box 109)
    - Moses Fleming 1948 (Box 109)
    - Fleming's Handy Market 1948-1952 (Box 109)
    - Franklin v. Yowell 1947 (Box 109)
    - Gentry v. Beatty; Beatty v. Connors 1942 (Box 109)
    - Goodwin v. St. Clair 1948 (Box 109)
    - Graham v. [?] 1948 (Box 109)
    - Samuel Green 1947-1950, 2 folders (Box 109)
    - Gwens v. Blackwell 1948 (Box 109)
    - Haggard v. Perry 1949 (Box 109)
    - Haigh v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 109)
    - Hall v. Amour and Co. 1947 (Box 109)
    - Halladay v. Johnson 1947-1948 (Box 110)
    - Halpin v. Sherman 1948-1949, 2 folders (Box 110)
    - Hamilton v. Central Electric and Gas Co. 1947-1948 (Box 110)
    - Haney v. Deane 1949 (Box 110)
    - Harris v. Harris 1948 (Box 110)
    - Bert C. Heath 1941 (Box 110)
    - Lindsay Heath, Jr. 1947-1948 (Box 110)
    - Henley v. New Culpepper Mills, Inc. 1948-1949 (Box 110)
    - Dewey G. Hensley 1948 (Box 110)
    - Hertz U-Drive-It v. Craver; Llorens v. Craver 1949 (Box 110)
    - Geraldine Hill for Matthew Hill 1949 (Box 110)
    - Huffman v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 110)
    - Humphries v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 110)
    - Hutchison v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 110)
    - Rosa Young Jackson 1948 (Box 110)
    - Jackson v. Farmer 1948-1949 (Box 110)
    - Jennings-Fogelman Case 1949 (Box 110)
    - Johnson v. Laird 1948-1950 (Box 110)
    - Johnson v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 110)
    - Johnson v. Bowers 1948 (Box 110)
    - James B. Johnson Estate 1946-1947, 2 folders (Box 110-111)
    - Thomas E. Johnson 1948-1949 (Box 111)
    - Jones v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948 (Box 111)
    - Jones v. Maule 1948 (Box 111)
    - Kent v. Osbourne 1949 (Box 111)
    - Kent v. Virginia Trailways 1949 (Box 111)
    - Kern v. Vest 1947 (Box 111)
    - Kindrich v. Ward 1948 (Box 111)
    - L. B. Kline Estate 1942-1947 (Box 111)
    - Walter Koren 1947-1951 (Box 111)
    - Lacks v. Granger 1949-1952 (Box 111)
    - Laird and Co. v. Ward 1947 (Box 111)
    - William Lambert 1948 (Box 111)
    - Lane and Barnett 1949 (Box 111)
    - LeBarron v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 111)
    - Lee v. Farinholt 1942 (Box 111)
    - Llewellyn v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948-1949 (Box 111)
    - Long v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948-1949 (Box 111)
    - Low v. Brown 1950-1951 (Box 111)
    - Low v. Holt 1944-1946, 14 folders (Box 111-112)
    - MacClammer v. MacClammer 1947 (Box 112)
    - Howard Marshall Estate 1949 (Box 112)
    - Mason v. Seiler 1949 (Box 112)
    - Master Arts Products v. Wood 1941 (Box 112)
    - Maupin v. Maupin 1942 (Box 112)
    - Moore v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948, 2 folders (Box 112)
    - Morris v. Sandridge 1948-1949 (Box 112)
    - Morris v. Dowell 1949 (Box 112)
    - Muceneek v. Bell 1948-1950 (Box 113)
    - National Cash Register Co. and R. P. Wilder 1947 (Box 113)
    - Nolan Finance v. Roseberry 1946-1947 (Box 113)
    - Obenschain v. Gibson 1949 (Box 113)
    - Obenschain v. Taylor 1949-1950 (Box 113)
    - Florence Pace 1949 (Box 113)
    - Parr v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 113)
    - Chester Payne 1947 (Box 113)
    - Payne v. Allstate 1947 (Box 113)
    - Pierce v. Shiflett 1947-1948 (Box 113)
    - Quarles v. Wignor 1949-1950 (Box 113)
    - Quarles v. Dickinson 1949 (Box 113)
    - Quarles v. Royal Swing 1948 (Box 113)
    - Estelle Quick 1948 (Box 113)
    - R. Radnitz 1947 (Box 113)
    - Fannie Ragland's heirs 1941-1942 (Box 113)
    - Reeves v. Reeves 1948-1949 (Box 113)
    - Richards v. Greenleaf 1940, 2 folders (Box 113)
    - Horace Chapman Richardson 1948 (Box 113)
    - Richardson v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948-1949 (Box 113)
    - Rigsby v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 113)
    - Roberts v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 113)
    - Parmer Rogers 1949 (Box 113)
    - A. S. Ronquist 1944 (Box 113)
    - Rubin v. Sherwood 1949-1953 (Box 113)
    - Lee Ryan 1941 (Box 113)
    - Ryder v. New Culpepper Mills, Inc. 1948 (Box 113)
    - Bettie Sandridge Estate 1942 (Box 113)
    - Sear v. McConchie 1949 (Box 113)
    - Segelbaum v. Frazer 1949 (Box 114)
    - Shiflett v. Commonwealth of Virginia 1947 (Box 114)
    - [Mary F. C.] Shiflett v. [James C.] Shiflett 1948, 3 folders (Box 114)
    - [Mary M.] Shiflett v. [Ben] Shiflett 1948 (Box 114)
    - Simmons v. Schrogham 1949 (Box 114)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. 1949, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. v. Roy Steam Laundry 1948 (Box 114)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. v. Ewing 1947-1948 (Box 114)
    - Charles D. Smith 1948 (Box 114)
    - Beverly D. Sprouse 1949-1953 (Box 114)
    - [Ruby J.] Sprouse v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948-1949 (Box 114)
    - [William D.] Sprouse v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1949 (Box 114)
    - Storey v. Montague 1948-1949 (Box 114)
    - Street v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948-1949 (Box 114)
    - Rubina D. Stuart 1940 (Box 114)
    - Supreme Construction v. Barbour 1941 (Box 114)
    - Sutherland v. Walker 1947 (Box 114)
    - Sutherland v. Flood 1948 (Box 114)
    - Sweitzer v. Stanley 1949-1950 (Box 114)
    - Swift and Co. v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1949 (Box 114)
    - Taylor Coal Co. v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 114)
    - Marcellus Terrell 1948-1950 (Box 114)
    - George M. Thayer 1948 (Box 114)
    - Mary Thomas Estate (Brown v. Gilmer) 1940's (Box 114-116)
    - Thomason v. Corey 1949 (Box 116)
    - Thompson v. New Culpepper Mills, Inc. 1948 (Box 116)
    - Francis Gwyne Thorpe i 1948-1949 (Box 116)
    - Roy O. Unruh 1941-1942 (Box 116)
    - Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. v. Staples 1949 (Box 116)
    - Walker v. Adams 1949 (Box 116)
    - Walker v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1947-1948 (Box 116)
    - Waller v. New Culpepper Mills, Inc. 1948 (Box 116)
    - Ward v. Laird and Co. 1948 (Box 116)
    - Ware v. Wood 1941, 1946 (Box 116)
    - White v. Fitzgerald, Sidney and Pugh 1949-1950 (Box 116)
    - L. G. White 1945-1953 (Box 116)
    - Wikman v. Home for Incurables 1945 (Box 116)
    - Wilson v. Hunt 1947 (Box 116)
    - Mary E. Wilson Estate (Wilson v. Brown) 1940's, 9 folders (Box 116-117)
    - Wood v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1948 (Box 117)
    - Wood v. Ritchie 1947 (Box 117)
    - Wood v. Central Electric and Power 1948 (Box 117)
    - Woody v. Laird and Co. 1947-1948 (Box 117)
    - Woody v. Virginia Stage Lines, Inc. 1948 (Box 117)
  - 1950's
    - Adams v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 118)
    - Alexander v. Travis 1950-1953 (Box 118)
    - Anchor Motor Freight v. Dale 1950-1951 (Box 118)
    - Anchor Motor Freight cases 1950-1951 (Box 118)
    - Associated Transport v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 118)
    - Associated Transport v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 118)
    - Balser v. City of Charlottesville 1951 (Box 118)
    - Bazzanella v. Fortin 1952 (Box 118)
    - Bennington v. Waldrop 1950-1951 (Box 118)
    - Bishop v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951-1952, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - James E. Blakey 1950-1951 (Box 118)
    - Bodie v. Smith 1950 (Box 118)
    - Bowles v. Laird and Co. 1952 (Box 118)
    - Branch v. Worley 1951-1952 (Box 118)
    - Breeden v. Pence 1951 (Box 118)
    - Thomas Bridgeford 1952 (Box 118)
    - Mary E. Brooks 1951 (Box 119)
    - Burbridge v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951-1952 (Box 119)
    - Byers v. Laird and Co. 1950 (Box 119)
    - Campbell and Croft 1953, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - Campbell v. Haggard 1952 (Box 119)
    - Chaplin v. Herrings 1952 (Box 119)
    - Chapman v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 119)
    - Chears v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 119)
    - Chisholm v. Burroughs 1950 (Box 119)
    - Clower v. Lipscomb 1950-1951 (Box 119)
    - Collier v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 119)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Brice 1951 (Box 119)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Proffitt 1950 (Box 119)
    - Courtney v. Queen of Charlotte Hotel 1952 (Box 119)
    - Crewes v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 119)
    - Dade v. Nowland 1950-1951 (Box 119)
    - Davis v. Meadow Gold Products Co. 1951 (Box 119)
    - Day v. Bamberger 1952 (Box 119)
    - Doss v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951-1952 (Box 119)
    - Draper v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 119)
    - Dudley v. City of Charlottesville 1950-1952 (Box 119)
    - Duke v. Lam 1950-1951 (Box 119)
    - Duke v. Simpson 1951 (Box 119)
    - Gilmer Gunn Estate 1951-1952, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Dupont v. Linke 1950 (Box 120)
    - Eastwood v. Howard Johnson 1950 (Box 120)
    - Edwards v. Stephenson 1950 (Box 120)
    - Edwards v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 120)
    - Estes v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Evans v. Evans 1952 (Box 120)
    - Ezekiel and Weilman Co. v. Weston 1951-1953 (Box 120)
    - Fanshaw v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 120)
    - Farrish v. Easton 1951 (Box 120)
    - Faulkner v. Bolling 1951 (Box 120)
    - Fincham v. Fitzhugh Drug Co. 1953 (Box 120)
    - Fischer v. Trainum 1950 (Box 120)
    - Fisher v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 120)
    - Foege v. Dravo Corporation 1950-1951 (Box 120)
    - Fox v. Miller 1950-1951 (Box 120)
    - Fridley v. Sinclair Refining Co. 1952 (Box 120)
    - Fritz v. Brodie 1952 (Box 120)
    - Carl and Douglas Gibson 1950 (Box 120)
    - Gitchell v. Sears Roebuck and Co. 1950-1951 (Box 120)
    - Victor E. Glick 1950 (Box 120)
    - Godwin v. Duke 1951 (Box 120)
    - Goldstein v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950 (Box 120)
    - Goodloe v. Andrews 1951 (Box 120)
    - Gough v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951, 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Grayson-Robinson Stores, Inc. v. Watts 1952-1954 (Box 120)
    - Greenwell v. Kiamie Textile Mills 1951 (Box 120)
    - Mary Carr Greer 1950 (Box 120)
    - Haggard v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 120)
    - Haney v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 121)
    - Marvin Haney 1950 (Box 121)
    - Harlowe v. Quaker Oats Co. 1950-1951 (Box 121)
    - J. R. Harper, Inc. 1952 (Box 121)
    - Hawkins v. Kiamie Textile Mills 1950-1951 (Box 121)
    - Hawkins v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951-1952 (Box 121)
    - Henderson v. Brown 1953 (Box 121)
    - J. C. Henley 1950 (Box 121)
    - Hollis M. Hensley 1951 (Box 121)
    - Hertz U-Drive-It v. Modena 1950, 2 folders (Box 121)
    - Hertz U-Drive-It v. Wheeler 1950 (Box 121)
    - Heuer v. Agee 1952 (Box 121)
    - Hill v. Hill 1951-1954 (Box 121)
    - Hinkel v. Gleason 1952 (Box 121)
    - John Edward Holford 1951 (Box 121)
    - Holland v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 121)
    - Huffman v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 121)
    - Hughes v. Short 1953 (Box 121)
    - Hunt v. Sears Roebuck and Co. 1950-1951 (Box 121)
    - Johnson v. Gentry 1950 (Box 121)
    - Jurgenson v. Jurgenson 1951-1952 (Box 121)
    - Keller v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 121)
    - B. D. Ladd 1950-1951 (Box 121)
    - Lannigan v. Yancy 1951 (Box 121)
    - Lego v. Cook 1951 (Box 121)
    - Louis W. Martin 1950 (Box 121)
    - McAllister v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 121)
    - McCallister v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 121)
    - James U. McClammer 1952 (Box 121)
    - Mehring v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 121)
    - Melton v. Bibb 1950 (Box 121)
    - Melton v. Hollingshead 1950 (Box 121)
    - Mereness v. Moubray 1950 (Box 121)
    - W. T. Michael 1950 (Box 121)
    - Miles v. Garrison 1954 (Box 122)
    - Miller v. Carpenter 1950-1951 (Box 122)
    - Morris v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 122)
    - Charles P. Mundorff 1950 (Box 122)
    - Nash v. Kiamie Textile Mills 1951 (Box 122)
    - Nolan v. Marsh 1951-1952 (Box 122)
    - Orner v. Pure Oil Co. 1952-1953 (Box 122)
    - Parr v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 122)
    - [A. H.] Payne v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 122)
    - [Margaret] Payne v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 122)
    - Peoples Mortgage Corp. 1952 (Box 122)
    - Perkins v. Brooks 1952 (Box 122)
    - Powell v. Whittington 1950 (Box 122)
    - Powell v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1952 (Box 122)
    - Profitt v. Brown 1950 (Box 122)
    - Pugh v. Sears Roebuck and Co. 1950 (Box 122)
    - Pure Oil Co. 1952-1953 (Box 122)
    - Pure Oil Co. v. Stratton 1952 (Box 122)
    - Putze v. Fortune 1950 (Box 122)
    - Richardsn v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950 (Box 122)
    - Rigsby v. Knight 1952 (Box 122)
    - Roberst v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951-1952 (Box 122)
    - Royall v. Dravo Corporation 1950-1951 (Box 122)
    - Saylor v. Laird and Co. 1951 (Box 122)
    - Schafer v. Vaden 1950 (Box 122)
    - Schleuter v. Dravo Corporation 1950-1951 (Box 122)
    - Sears and Roebuck Co. 1950 (Box 122)
    - Sears Roebuck and Co. v. Cities Service Oil Co. 1951 (Box 122)
    - Sears Roebuck and Co. v. Copenhaver 1950 (Box 122)
    - Sears Roebuck and Co. v. Ray 1951 (Box 122)
    - Seay v. Anchor Motor Freight 1950-1951, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Shepherd v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950 (Box 123)
    - Joseph Silverman 1951 (Box 123)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. 1951-1952 (Box 123)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. v. Jones 1950 (Box 123)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. v. Keller 1952 (Box 123)
    - Sinclair Refining Co. v. Snead 1951 (Box 123)
    - Matilda Sjostrom 1952 (Box 123)
    - Ellen M. Slayden Estate 1950 (Box 123)
    - Smith v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1951 (Box 123)
    - Smith v. Jessee 1951 (Box 123)
    - Stallings v. Kiamie Textile Mills 1951 (Box 123)
    - Strawhun v. Fish Contractors, Inc. 1950 (Box 123)
    - Sublett v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950-1951 (Box 123)
    - Sullivan v. Wertz 1952 (Box 123)
    - Thomas v. Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1950 (Box 123)
    - Thomason v. Payne 1950 (Box 123)
    - E. A. Turner and Joe Walker 1950-1951 (Box 123)
    - Unfiled case materials n.d. (Box 123)
    - Via v. Gibson 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Booker 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Carpenter 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Furr 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Guy Johnson Lumber and Supply Co. 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Holland 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Hughes Service Station 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Hupp 1951-1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Kemper 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Marshall 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. McCraw 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Morris 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Mottley Construction Co. 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Reaves 1951 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Snow's Nursery 1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Talley 1951-1952 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. v. Wood 1951 (Box 123)